[{"answer": "I beg your pardon, brother. What did you say you were hunting", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Fossils, huh", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Fossils, huh", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " A what", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'm a paleontologist", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "A paleontologist", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You see, from this vertebrae I shall be able to reconstruct the entire skeleton", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "It was the vertebrae of a Megatherium", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I beg your pardon", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Good morning.  Look here, young man", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I didn't care for 'sister' last night, and I don't like 'Lovey' this morning. My name is my friend", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I see", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "That's ridiculous", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "It certainly is", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, Mr. my friend, for a man who is supposed to be a leader, your d", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't know. I'm a paleontologist, not a Foreign Secretary", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "In that event, we better make arrangements to get some porters immediately. Some means to get us back to civilization", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "As far away as I ever want to be", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Of course, the porters will be very well paid", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No porters here!", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm afraid that wouldn't help. You see, we have no porters here", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " How about you my friend? Come on. Let's you and I play a game of honeymoon bridge", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Thinking? What about some double solitaire", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What could there be except just another hill? In any event, I'm not curious. At the moment, it seems to me we should be concerned about getting home. I'd give anything to be in that place right now", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What do you mean if we should get out", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What do you mean if we should get out", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " That's what you said", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Our Valley is very rich in a metal called gold, which fortunately for us is valued very highly in the outside world. So we merely . . ", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Buy and", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Porters", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Oh, you've read my books. You do more things! What have my books got to do with it", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "A man whose life was empty", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Then it's done", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Thank you", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, no. You see, I got this plumbing busines", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Oh, no", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "It's no place for you, my friend. Think of what's waiting for you. Do you want to stay here until you're half dead? Until your mind starts corroding like the rest of them", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You've got to talk about it. What about me? You said they stole that plane to bring you here. I didn't want to come. You owe me some responsibility", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " Lucky thing for me you snapped out of it, too. You saved my life. I never could have made it alone", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "was sayin", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What's happened? Where's my friend", "docId": "Lost_Horizon.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Going", "qsentId": 44}]